http://www.elwinsoft.com/terms.html

Terms of use
HomeDownloadFeedbackSite mapEnglishAttributeMagic Profor Documents editionStandard editionElwinsoft (Elwinsoft.com) makes available information, materials, and products on this Web site, subject to the following terms and conditions. By accessing this Web site, you agree to the terms and conditions herein. Elwinsoft reserves the right to change these terms and conditions at any time without notice. The most current version of the Terms of Use can be reviewed by clicking on the "Terms of Use" hypertext link located at the bottom of our Web pages.
Copyright
The information on this Web site is protected by copyright:
Copyright© 2001-12, Roman Ish (www.elwinsoft.com). All Rights Reserved.
Except as specifically permitted herein, no portion of the information on this Web site may be reproduced in any form or by any means without prior written permission from Elwinsoft.
Use of Software
The software and accompanying materials available to download from this Site are the copyrighted work of Elwinsoft. Use of the software is governed by the terms of the end user license agreement included with such software. If no license accompanies the download, the terms of the license which accompanied the original product being updated will govern. You will not be able to use, download, or install any software unless you agree to the terms of such end user license agreement. Absent a license agreement that accompanies the software, use of the software will be governed by this terms and conditions. You agree that you will not decompile, reverse engineer, or otherwise attempt to discover the source code of the software available on the Site.	Use of the Site Information
Except as otherwise indicated on this Site, you may view, print, copy, and distribute documents on this Site subject to the following terms and conditions:
The document may be used solely for informational, personal, non-commercial purposes;
Any copy of the document or portion thereof must include all copyright and proprietary notices in the same form and manner as on the original.
The document may not be modified in any way.
Elwinsoft reserves the right to revoke such authorization at any time, and any such use shall be discontinued immediately upon notice.
Warranties and Disclaimers
EXCEPT AS EXPRESSLY PROVIDED OTHERWISE IN AN AGREEMENT BETWEEN YOU AND ELWINSOFT, ALL INFORMATION AND SOFTWARE ON THIS WEB SITE IS PROVIDED "AS IS" WITHOUT ANY OTHER WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, OR THOSE ARISING BY LAW, STATUTE, USAGE OF TRADE, OR COURSE OF DEALING. ELWINSOFT ASSUMES NO RESPONSIBILITY FOR ERRORS OR OMISSIONS IN THE INFORMATION OR SOFTWARE OR OTHER DOCUMENTS WHICH ARE REFERENCED BY OR LINKED TO THIS WEB SITE.
REFERENCES TO CORPORATIONS, THEIR SERVICES AND PRODUCTS, ARE PROVIDED "AS IS" WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED. IN NO EVENT SHALL ELWINSOFT BE LIABLE FOR ANY SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, INDIRECT OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OF ANY KIND, OR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, THOSE RESULTING FROM LOSS OF USE, DATA OR PROFITS, WHETHER OR NOT ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF DAMAGE, AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE USE, RELIANCE ON, OR PERFORMANCE OF THIS INFORMATION.
THIS WEB SITE COULD INCLUDE TECHNICAL OR OTHER INACCURACIES OR TYPOGRAPHICAL ERRORS. CHANGES ARE PERIODICALLY ADDED TO THE INFORMATION HEREIN; THESE CHANGES WILL BE INCORPORATED IN NEW EDITIONS OF THIS WEB SITE. ELWINSOFT MAY MAKE IMPROVEMENTS AND/OR CHANGES IN THE PRODUCT(S) AND/OR THE PROGRAM(S) DESCRIBED IN THIS WEB SITE AT ANY TIME.Revisions and Errata
The materials appearing on Elwinsoft's web site could include technical, typographical, or photographic errors.
Elwinsoft does not warrant that any of the materials on its web site are accurate, complete, or current.
Elwinsoft may make changes to the materials contained on its web site at any time without notice.
Elwinsoft does not, however, make any commitment to update the materials.Links
Elwinsoft has not reviewed all of the sites linked to its Internet web site and is not responsible for the contents of any such linked site.
The inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by Elwinsoft of the site. Use of any such linked web site is at the user's own risk.Site Terms of Use Modifications
Elwinsoft may revise these terms of use for its web site at any time without notice.
By using this web site you are agreeing to be bound by the then current version of these Terms and Conditions of Use.Governing Law
Any claim relating to Elwinsoft's web site shall be governed by the laws of the State of c_state without regard to its conflict of law provisions.Privacy Policy
Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.
Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.
We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.
© Elwinsoft, 1999-2017
HomeDownloadTerms of useFeedbackSite map
